Meriç ÇAPAR

Konyaaltı/Antalya

linkedin.com/in/meriç-çapar-770ba3159

+90 536 211 70 30 | mericcaparrr@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am third year Computer Engineering student with various volunteer experiences in different NGOs. I had a chance to develop my leadership and teamwork skills through experience working on complex initiatives with cross-functional teams in a very fast-moving environment.

KNOWLEDGE & SKILLS

- Fluent in both written and spoken English
- Understanding of SQL and Python
- Understanding of Numpy, Pandas, Seaborn, Plotly
- Good command of MC Office Programs
- Ability to work with individuals of different nationalities and cultures
- Developed communication skills, ability to simplify complex topics for broad audience

- Detail-oriented and strong sense of ownership for projects
- Creative in finding new solutions and designing innovative systems and processes
- The ability to remain calm in any situation
- Developed problem solving, resolutionand decision-making skills

EDUCATION

Isparta Suleyman Demirel University

Computer Engineering Student / 3rd year.

Isparta 09.2020 -Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

SDÜ BIDB – Süleyman Demirel Üniversitesi Bilgi İşlem Daire Başkanlığı

Part Time Computer Technician

09.2020 - 03.2023

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

BEST - Board of European Students of Technology

Information Technology Coordinator of BEST Isparta
PAX Responsible of BEST Isparta 2018 Course

09.2021-06.2023 04.2021 - 05.2021

SOCIAL ATTRIBUTES

Hobbies& Interests

• Travelling, Coding, Gaming, Swimming.

REFERENCES

Available on request.